let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the real name of Iron Man?",
    answer: "Tony Stark",
    options: [
      "Steve Rogers",
      "Tony Stark",
      "Bruce Banner",
      "Peter Parker"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which Infinity Stone is located on Vormir?",
    answer: "Soul Stone",
    options: [
      "Time Stone",
      "Space Stone",
      "Soul Stone",
      "Power Stone"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is Captain America's shield made of?",
    answer: "Vibranium",
    options: [
      "Adamantium",
      "Vibranium",
      "Titanium",
      "Uru"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which hero wields Mjolnir?",
    answer: "Thor",
    options: [
      "Loki",
      "Hulk",
      "Thor",
      "Odin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who is the director of S.H.I.E.L.D.?",
    answer: "Nick Fury",
    options: [
      "Phil Coulson",
      "Nick Fury",
      "Maria Hill",
      "Tony Stark"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the entity that grants Spider-Man his powers?",
    answer: "Radioactive Spider",
    options: [
      "Radioactive Spider",
      "Gamma Radiation",
      "Super Soldier Serum",
      "Alien Symbiote"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which planet is Thanos originally from?",
    answer: "Titan",
    options: [
      "Asgard",
      "Sakaar",
      "Titan",
      "Xandar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the real name of Black Panther?",
    answer: "T'Challa",
    options: [
      "M'Baku",
      "T'Challa",
      "N'Jadaka",
      "Shuri"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which Marvel character is known for breaking the fourth wall?",
    answer: "Deadpool",
    options: [
      "Spider-Man",
      "Deadpool",
      "Ant-Man",
      "Doctor Strange"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who created Ultron?",
    answer: "Tony Stark and Bruce Banner",
    options: [
      "Tony Stark and Bruce Banner",
      "Wanda Maximoff",
      "Thanos",
      "Hank Pym"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What metal is Captain America's shield primarily composed of?",
    answer: "Vibranium",
    options: [
      "Adamantium",
      "Vibranium",
      "Steel",
      "Iron"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which Marvel hero has the ability to shrink in size?",
    answer: "Ant-Man",
    options: [
      "Ant-Man",
      "The Wasp",
      "Hulk",
      "Spider-Man"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is Doctor Strange's real name?",
    answer: "Stephen Strange",
    options: [
      "Stephen Strange",
      "Stephen Strange Jr.",
      "Stephen Strange III",
      "Stephen Rogers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which Marvel hero was frozen in ice for decades?",
    answer: "Captain America",
    options: [
      "Winter Soldier",
      "Captain America",
      "Iron Man",
      "Hawkeye"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the name of Peter Quill's alter ego?",
    answer: "Star-Lord",
    options: [
      "Rocket",
      "Star-Lord",
      "Gamora",
      "Drax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Who is the main villain in 'Black Panther'?",
    answer: "Erik Killmonger",
    options: [
      "Erik Killmonger",
      "Ulysses Klaue",
      "M'Baku",
      "Zuri"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which Marvel character wields the hammer Stormbreaker?",
    answer: "Thor",
    options: [
      "Thor",
      "Loki",
      "Odin",
      "Hela"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "What is the source of Hulk's powers?",
    answer: "Gamma Radiation",
    options: [
      "Super Soldier Serum",
      "Gamma Radiation",
      "Radioactive Spider",
      "Alien Symbiote"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Who is the Scarlet Witch?",
    answer: "Wanda Maximoff",
    options: [
      "Wanda Maximoff",
      "Jean Grey",
      "Rogue",
      "Mystique"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which Marvel hero is known as the 'Merc with a Mouth'?",
    answer: "Deadpool",
    options: [
      "Deadpool",
      "Spider-Man",
      "Iron Man",
      "Ant-Man"
    ]
  }
];
